Dad!
Give my daughter back.
Or…
I won't leave,
even if you run me over a thousand times.
Don't chicken out.
Floor it!
Run him over!
Dad!
Don't hit my dad!
Give my daughter…
back.
Turn around. Run.
That's what you get
for running over my dad!
How can you run over my dad!
Sir!
That's what you get
for running over my dad!
-Xiaohe.
-How dare you!
-Quick.
-Dad!
Dad!
Dad! Wake up!
Don't sleep. Dad!
Wake up.
Wake up, Dad! Dad!
Xiaohe.
I'm fine.
Am I rocking it
today?
-Wake up, Dad!
-Sir!
Don't sleep!
Sir.
-Quick. Call an ambulance.
-Okay.
Sir!
Hurry. Drag him out. Quick.
-Wake up! Don't sleep, sir!
-How is he?
His bones are fine.
Sir. Sir. Don't sleep.
Mei said there was a roadblock
on the highway.
Turn left at the next intersection.
There's a workshop.
He'll be waiting for us there.
Uncle Ran.
The human traffickers are there.
HOMELY WORKSHOP
AHAO AUTO MAINTENANCE
POLICE
Qu.
This is the only construction area
within all three schools.
Only this spot
doesn't have security cameras.
Let's get to work.
Mister, I need your help.
Have you seen these kids?
Do you know anyone here who gives rides?
No.
Have you seen these kids?
-Have you seen these five kids?
-No.
I don't know them.
I don't have a car.
I always use a trolley to restock.
All right then.
Wait.
Someone who gives rides?
You can ask that shop.
The owner loves to give people rides
when he restocks.
He is quite scary-looking.
I heard that he was imprisoned once
for kidnapping.
Gaoyishou?
The chef is on a break.
We open at five.
Where is your boss?
We're from the Nanshan Branch.
We're asking about people giving rides.
He went home to sleep.
Please return at 4:30 p.m.
Stand right there!
It hurts! Madam. Not so rough.
It hurts!
Not so rough.
Not so rough. It hurts.
PROSPEROUS BUSINESS
I've never given kids a ride.
You can check the dashcam in my car.
What's with your criminal record
of kidnapping?
Who told you that?
Was it the woman from--
Just answer my question.
I already served my sentence.
What more do you want?
Fine.
It was an argument with my wife.
My wife…
Well, my ex-wife
returned to her parents' place
to hide from me.
I was mad,
so I kidnapped her and starved her.
I was jailed for three years.
Mr. Officer.
I give people rides
when I'm out restocking.
Is that a crime?
Do you have to pin me down and arrest me?
Why did you run just now?
I was arrested once.
Whenever I see police officers,
my legs begin moving before I know it.
Dad.
What?
Isn't she the host on the TV channel?
That's him.
I can recognize him,
even if he has turned into ashes.
Mei.
He's still in Weiyang.
Why aren't they picking up?
Hello, Officer He?
Hey, Ms. Wang.
Can you check if there are
needlestick injuries on Han Zi'ang?
Officer He. I found some.
I found two on his right arm.
Mei is a regular
among the wanted criminals.
He is involved
in many child trafficking cases.
He is cunning and good
at disguising himself.
He has not been arrested
for more than a decade.
Based on the information given
by Officer He Xiaohe,
we can deduce
that Mei lurks around
the construction area near Fuxing Street.
He stalks students who skip classes
to hang out at the illegal internet cafe.
Then, he injects them with anesthetics
before kidnapping them.
The last victim, Han Zi'ang,
is quite different
from the four previous victims.
We believe that after Han Zi'ang
left the internet cafe,
he didn't go home.
Instead, he went to the 18th floor
of New York Block
to explore out of curiosity.
Help! Help! Help!
Help! Help!
After Han Zi'ang,
there has been no new victim.
PERSON OF INTEREST: MEI
That means Han Zi'ang's escape
disrupted Mei's plan.
He had no choice but to stop.
His priority now
is to bring those four victims
out of Weiyang.
Bai, Hui. Print out the wanted posters.
Make sure the photo is huge.
Then, let others post them everywhere.
Xing. Investigate
all egresses of the city.
Check the cameras of bus stations
and train stations
to see if the culprit
-has left Weiyang with the victims.
-Got it.
Mangkun. Bring some men with you
and investigate the motels, hostels,
or warehouses of the district.
The culprit might be hiding
the victims there
before buyers appear.
Guys. Split up.
Xiaohe,
you provided a useful lead.
I allow you to work
with the Special Task Force.
Thank you, sir.
But given the urgency,
is casting your net wide
the best way to do it?
If not, we wait for Mei
to turn himself in?
-But… But we are running out--
-Sorry. Captain Qu.
Xiaohe. Let's go.
Why?
Your deposition was excellent.
And your dad is almost recovered.
Xiaohe,
I owe you an apology.
It was my fault.
I was too harsh on you.
If I had put myself in your shoes,
things wouldn't have ended this way.
You wouldn't have run into danger.
I ask for your forgiveness.
No need to apologize.
I made this mess.
And I will own up.
You have no idea
how worried your dad was
when he heard that you were in danger.
He hailed a cab overnight at Mount Wu
and traveled over 400 kilometers here.
I know.
When he stood before the van,
I already knew it.
Xiaohe.
It's okay, Uncle Ran.
Don't worry about me.
And no need to console me.
I'm strong.
Anyway, what happened
to Melon and the rest?
Who?
Those four guys on the esports team.
After you raided the internet cafe,
are they homeless now?
Aren't we heading home?
Eat slowly.
Oh. Have you found a new base?
We have been thinking a lot lately.
There is no future in esports.
It's better to go back home.
We plan to work
in a factory after the Chinese New Year.
Who says there's no future in esports?
It's the 21st century.
As long as you work with computers,
you have a future.
Besides, all of you have worked
and trained so hard.
If you don't have a match
with someone else,
you'll bring shame to your own hard work.
Exactly.
What about the eggs I bought you guys?
I know several cheap
and legit internet cafes.
All of you will go to the police station
to get your identity cards done
to prove that you're adults.
Then, you can practice there.
Here.
Consider this an investment from me.
Once you become popular,
visit the Criminal Department
and pay me back.
Thank you, Officer Ran.
Dig in.
Come. An extra braised egg for you.
You're awesome, Uncle Ran.
You're my idol for life.
I'm so proud of you.
Another chicken drumstick for you.
What?
Is my cholesterol not high enough?
Forget it then.
You can't put food
in my bowl and take it away.
Uncle Ran,
Melon and the guys
are ambitious, aren't they?
They are good kids.
They work hard and are committed.
Why else did I give them
two months of my salary?
Then,
perhaps you should
support my dream as well.
I want to study music in Beijing.
I work hard and am committed.
Music is not a proper job.
Your priority now is to study
and get into a good university.
You were brave and smart inside the van
with the human traffickers.
You can be a criminal police officer.
Do you want to join the police force
and make use of your talent?
Actually,
being an officer like you sounds cool.
You
will never be an excellent cop like Ran.
Excuse me?
I am just as smart as him,
and I'm stronger than him.
You can have your opinion.
I won't stop you.
Just promise me
that you'll study hard.
After you graduate from high school,
I'll send you to Beijing to study music.
Why not after middle school?
You have to graduate first.
Be a literate rock artist.
He's right.
Don't just rock and roll.
-Deal.
We don't do that anymore.
Deal.
I will study now then.
She is skipping her meal.
Sir.
Xiaohe wrote this song.
Listen to it when you're free.
I think she's good.
-Really?
-Yes.
RESTRICTED AREA
Let's have a drink.
Sir.
Your body hasn't recovered.
The doctor said you shouldn't drink.
For this occasion, we must.
Without you,
my family would be all gone.
I would be all alone for real.
Thank you.
Back then in the hospital,
you told me not to be sappy.
Look who's being sappy now.
Right.
Oh, sir.
Did you find anything useful on your trip?
I told you not to drink,
but you wouldn't listen.
Have some water.
Sir,
I'll request the higher-ups
to give you a longer break.
HE YUANHANG, SECOND-CLASS MERIT
I can't take my wage
without working for it.
I want to give it one last shot
and investigate Yuanlongli again.
Even if I find nothing in the end,
at the very least, I can close
the chapter once and for all.
MISSING PERSON TURNED INTO KIDNAP
FOUR TEENAGERS STILL MISSING
ARE THE POLICE USELESS?
ARE THEY DEAD OR ALIVE?
How many days till the deadline?
Captain Qu. Permission
to assign several policemen
to assist me.
I want to give it my last shot.
Captain Qu.
I'd like to work with Xiaohe.
I want to work with Xiaohe too.
He is the support I found for us.
Old He, help us show them
what we're capable of.
Old He?
Who are you calling old here?
Sorry.
Perhaps we should just call you Mr. He.
-Say it.
-Mr. He.
That's nice.
Mr. He,
how will we investigate Yuanlongli?
Mei is involved in many abduction cases.
He is cunning and good at disguising.
We cannot predict what he will do
by using a logical mind.
For a serial abductor,
the most dangerous place
is the safest place.
That's how they hide under our noses.
Dad. Just cut to the chase.
Yuanlongli will be redeveloped soon.
Many residents have moved away.
All those empty units
are the perfect hiding spot for Mei.
Dad, how come you are so sure
that Mei will be hiding under our noses?
I'm not sure.
But I have a feeling
that there's something more
hiding in Yuanlongli.
Officer He, you came to work again.
Ma Qiang. Fire safety
is very important during winter.
-All of you…
-Officer He.
Officer He, you're here again.
Honestly though, he has worked
as a policeman for so long.
He finally cracked a big case
and got a Second-Class Merit.
Also, it was Officer Ran
who let him claim the credit.
I also heard that his health is bad.
He is claiming disability aid now.
Wasn't the case closed already?
Why is he still in Yuanlongli?
He can't move on.
He needs to feel useful.
Go. Carry it. Quick.
You two. It's good enough.
Good enough. Hurry up now.
Hurry up.
Oh my!
Officer He.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to look for leads.
Give me the keys to the management office
of New York Block.
The keys…
Follow me to the office.
Come.
Officer He.
The keys?
What did you do?
I… We are building a cement block.
Seriously?
A cement block here?
Many people walk here. It's inconvenient.
I'm trying to be considerate.
The workers push
their wheelbarrows around.
A barricade here
can remind them not to hit anyone.
The keys.
Let's go.
WEIYANG PUBLIC SECURITY
BUREAU NANSHAN BRANCH
POLICE BY THE PEOPLE
FOR THE PEOPLE
I was looking for you, Fangxu.
Mei's accomplices confessed everything.
But they do not know where his base is.
Their communication
has always been unilateral.
Grab a screenshot
from the internet cafe's footage.
Then, update Mei's photo
-in our internal system.
-Okay.
Madam. Madam. Madam.
I'm looking for the criminal police.
What's the matter?
I want to report a case.
Come. Let's get you registered first.
It's urgent. I need to report a case.
Wu.
-Captain Ran.
-Madam.
Why are you looking
for the criminal police?
I want to report a case.
A murder in Yuanlongli.
This place is foul.
I rented this place for three years,
and I had to pay for so many things.
Buddy,
are you looking for a place to stay?
Run away now.
This place only has bad luck.
It's haunted.
Just run. Save yourself.
Whoever stays here is cursed.
HUAINAN TEMPLE
Mister,
you seem troubled.
Allow me to draw you
an evil-cleansing talisman.
Come.
Don't be so rough. Please.
-Don't be so rough.
-Spread superstitions again
-and I will arrest you.
-Don't be so rough.
Don't be so rough.
RAN
-Don't be so rough.
-Shut up.
-Sir.
-It hurts.
Where are you?
Where else can I be?
Come back to the station.
Let me investigate the floor first.
No need.
We may no longer need to visit Yuanlongli.
I'm not scared.
I have money.
I can kill many people,
and others will take the blame for me.
You can't do anything.
You can't do anything to me!
You have two options.
One, I'll burn the photos,
and you'll go somewhere to lay low.
Two,
I'll send the photos and the recording
to the police.
Do you want your freedom and money?
It's your choice.
Director Li of Dongshan Mine
killed himself inside the police station
five years ago.
Today, his surviving wife
came to report a case.
She claimed to have found
Director Li's hidden photos
and recordings when she was moving out.
This suggests Director Li
coerced Song Qingsong into leaving.
But how did Director Li get these photos?
Only two people had the opportunity
to give Director Li the photos.
Cripple Du. Wu Shanlong.
I'm inclined to believe
it was Wu Shanlong.
After all, he stood to profit the most
after Song Qingsong left.
We also found a photocopy
of the tender document
inside Wu Shanlong's home.
While he refused to admit
that he kept the document,
it doesn't mean
that he didn't use the photocopy
to blackmail Song Qingsong.
I even suspect
that the blackmailing letter
written to Song Qingsong by Xu Meng
was forged by him.
Song Qingsong never would have thought
that his brother-in-law was the one
who sabotaged him.
Unfortunately, she failed to escape.
The main culprit, Wu Shanlong, is dead.
The one who hired a hitman, Song Qingsong,
fled abroad for many years.
All we can do now
is to release a wanted poster.
But I don't understand one thing.
Wu Shanlong isn't smart.
How could he devise so many plans?
Ms. Zhao, you're out.
Ms. Zhao, you look so beautiful.
After our new treatment,
you look younger and prettier.
I have solid genes. My heels.
XINXIN BEAUTY SALON
Young girls like you
shouldn't just chase
after physical beauty blindly.
A woman's real charisma
doesn't come from her face,
but here.
Ms. Zhao. The balance
on your membership card is running low.
Do you want to…
Top up another 10,000 yuan.
How generous of you, Ms. Zhao.
Men are unreliable.
As women, we should treat ourselves.
See you.
Bye, Ms. Zhao.
Come back again.
Drive safely.
I'm so sick of her.
Listen.
She used to open
a foot massage parlor too.
She found a guy called Wu Shanlong,
and they both took over a cement factory.
That's how she became rich.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
So, she still relied on a man in the end.
YUANLONGLI INTERNATIONAL GARDEN
Ma Qiang. Give me the list of Yuanlongli's
current residents and tenants.
Several copies of it.
Officer He, what is this for?
Just do what you're told.
How many units have been vacated?
Many.
They are marked in red there.
2015 YUANLONGLI PROPERTY
OWNER/TENANT ROSTER
It seems like we have a busy night ahead.
Let's split up.
Zheng Zhong, you, Bai, and Hui
are in charge of Floors 1 to 9.
Xiaohe and I will check the ones upstairs.
Use the walkie-talkie
if you find anything.
Understood.
DEMOLITION
The vacant units on the eastern side
of the 4th floor
are 13 and 16.
Let's check 13 first.
It hurts! Be gentle. It hurts!
Shut up!
An escape room?
Do you even have the license for it?
It's so late at night.
You're doing this instead of sleeping.
This is a nuisance, do you hear me?
Sorry, sir.
We've made a mistake.
We'll leave now.
-Now.
-Go.
Sorry, sir.
Sorry. Sorry.
Mr. He. Mr. He.
We've searched all nine floors.
Nothing unusual.
Copy.
RESIDENTS
TENANTS REGISTRATION FORM
RESIDENT, TENANT, RESIDENT
Dad, Mei loves to use a fake identity.
He can rent a place using a fake identity.
How many tenants are here?
HE YIQIANG
HAO YOUQIANG
QIANG WEI'AN, WU QIANGYI, WANG ZIQIANG
Check this one first.
HE YIQIANG
Why?
Mei's fake identities
always have three characters.
And it always contains Qiang.
1316, ZHAO SONGLI, HE YIQIANG
Bai, Hui, Zheng Zhong.
Regroup at 1316 now. Now.
I'll go to Ma Qiang and call the owner.
Make sure to follow
the emergency break-in protocol later.
Okay.
Dad.